[
    {
        "id": "question1",
        "question": "Which country invented tea?",
        "options": [
            "India",
            "Malta",
            "China",
            "Vietnam"
        ],
        "answer": "China",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question2",
        "question": "Which is the only vowel on a standard keyboard that is not on the top line of letters?",
        "options": [
            "A",
            "B",
            "C",
            "D"
        ],
        "answer": "A",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question3",
        "question": "Hg is the chemical symbol of which element?",
        "options": [
            "Boron",
            "Carbon",
            "Argon",
            "Mercury"
        ],
        "answer": "Mercury",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question4",
        "question": "The fear referred to as arachnophobia indicates a fear of what?",
        "options": [
            "Water",
            "Spiders",
            "Death",
            "Females"
        ],
        "answer": "Spiders",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question5",
        "question": " The colored part of the human eye that controls how much light passes through the pupil is called?",
        "options": [
            "Pupil",
            "Iris",
            "Scapula",
            "Cornea"
        ],
        "answer": "Cornea",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question6",
        "question": "Which company owns Bugatti, Lamborghini, Audi, Porsche, and Ducati?",
        "options": [
            "Volkswagen",
            "Space X",
            "Pied Piper",
            "Kia"
        ],
        "answer": "Volkswagen",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question7",
        "question": " How many football players should each team have on the field at the start of each match?",
        "options": [
            "22",
            "14",
            "11",
            "6"
        ],
        "answer": "11",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question8",
        "question": "Which Jamaican runner is an 11-time world champion and holds the record in the 100 and 200-meter race?",
        "options": [
            "Mo Farah",
            "Ismail Lo",
            "Yohan Blake",
            "Usain Bolt"
        ],
        "answer": "Usain Bolt",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question9",
        "question": "What’s a “king” honeybee called?",
        "options": [
            "Drone",
            "Mare",
            "Kunta",
            "Kong"
        ],
        "answer": "Drone",
        "isAnswered": false
    },
    {
        "id": "question10",
        "question": "Which animal has the largest eye in the world?",
        "options": [
            "The giant squid",
            "The blue whale",
            "Great white",
            "Octopus"
        ],
        "answer": "The giant squid",
        "isAnswered": false
    }
]